var questions= [{
"question": "1.Entomology is the science that studies",
"option1": "A. Behavior of human beings",
"option2": "B. Insects",
"option3": "C. The origin and history of technical and scientific terms",                                                                   
"option4": "D. The formation of rocks",  
"answer": "2"
}, {
"question": "2.Name of the screen that recognizes touch input is :",
"option1": "A. Recog screen",
"option2": "B. Point Screen",
"option3": "C. Touch Screen",
"option4": "D. Android Screen",
"answer": "3"
}, {
"question": "3.Grand Central Terminal, Park Avenue, New York is the world's",
"option1": "A. largest railway station",
"option2": "B. highest railway station",
"option3": "C. longest railway station",
"option4": "D. None of the above",
"answer": "1"
}, {
"question": "4.Chief component of first generation computer was",
"option1": "A. Vacuum Tubes and Valves",
"option2": "B. Transistors",
"option3": "C. Integrated Circuits",
"option4": "D. All of above",
"answer": "1"
}, {
"question": "5.Microprocessors as switching devices are for which generation computers",
"option1": "A. First Generation",
"option2": "B. Second Generation",
"option3": "C. Third Generation",
"option4": "D. Fourth Generation",
"answer": "4"
}, {
"question": "6.Garampani sanctuary is located at",
"option1": "A. Asia",
"option2": "B. Africa",
"option3": "C. Europe",
"option4": "D. Australia",
"answer": "2"
}, {
"question": "7.Regarding a VDU, Which statement is more correct?",
"option1": "A. It is a peripheral device",
"option2": "B. It is hardware item",
"option3": "C. It is an input device",
"option4": "D. It is an output device",
"answer": "1"
},{
"question": "8.Hitler party which came into power in 1933 is known as",
"option1": "A. Labour Party",
"option2": "B. Nazi Party",
"option3": "C. Ku-Klux-Klan",
"option4": "D. Democratic Party",
"answer": "2"
},{
"question": "9.Euclid was",
"option1": "A. Greek mathematician",
"option2": "B. Contributor to the use of deductive principles of logic as the basis of geometry",
"option3": "C. Propounded the geometrical theorems",
"option4": "D. All of the above",
"answer": "4"
}, {
"question": "10.Filaria is caused by",
"option1": "A. Bacteria",
"option2": "B. Mosquito",
"option3": "C. Protozoa",
"option4": "D. Virus",
"answer": "2"
}];

